How could you let
Baltazar Bratt
just get away!
You're fired!
He is really good to snuggle with...
Agness what are you doing?
Since you don't have a job...I just wanted to help!
Excuse me...
Hey... could you....?
of course.
..Now
As I was saying...
Goodbye!
Seriously?
I really must....
...have a word with you
on behalf of your twin brother
Dru
What?
Twin brother?
I can't wait to meet my brother!
Brother!!
Who doesn't love this guy?
Look at him!
Oh! The hair will make you better
Look at his face!
Oh! He's so mad.
You must be his beautiful wife
Sweet daughter
This place is amazing.
It's mine I guess sure...
I'm not really into things.
Face it, Gru!
Villain is in your blood!
You ready to continue the family tradition?
You and me?
No!
I left that life behind me.
Just one night !
I'm going in.
I'm going to be impaled!
Haha, I'm Okay.
This does not mean that you're going back to be villains
Bueno?.....