Doctor Strange
You think you know how the world works?
What if I told you
the reality you know is one of many?
This doesn't make any sense
Not everything does
Not everything has to
Through the mystic arts, we harness energy
and shape reality
We travel great distances
in an instant
How do I get from here to there?
How did you become a doctor?
Study and practice, years of it
What the...
There's a strength to him - But is he ready?
Be careful which path you travel down, Strange
Stronger men than you have lost their way
I am death
and pain
You'll die protecting this world
I can't do this
There is no other way
I've spent so many years
hearing through time
looking for you
And what's this? My mantra?
The Wi-Fi password
We're not savages