What's up, guys?
So, to become an Avenger
are there like trials, or...an interview?
Do me a favor. Can't you just be a friendly neighbourhood Spider-Man?
Just... stay close to the ground.
You're the Spider-Man! From YouTube!
Can you summon an army of spiders?
No, Ned. No...
Do you know him, too?
I stole his shield.
Can I try the suit on?
Badass.
The rich and the powerful, like Stark
they don't care about us.
The world's changing, boys.
It's time that we change, too.
His weapons are crazy dangerous!
Listen, Peter, forget the flying monster guy.
There are people who handle this sort of thing.
Your legal weapon barrel was at 2:30.
You missed it!
What if somebody died?
I was just trying to be like you.
I wanted you to be better.
I'm gonna need the suit back.
But I'm nothing without this suit!
If you're nothing without this suit, then you shouldn't have it.
I screwed up
You need to stop carrying the weight of the world on your shoulders.
I want you to understand
I'll do anything to protect my family.
I know you know what I'm talking about...
..so don't mess with me.
Cuz I will kill you
and everybody you love.
My friend's up there!
That guy is still out there.
I've just got to do this on my own.
Just... don't do anything stupid.
I got this!
Alright?
Yeah