There are days that define your story beyond your life
Like the day they arrived
What might be called "first contact".The objects measure at least...
I'm Colonel G.T. Weber from the intelligence. Pack your bags
You are at the top of everyone's list when it comes to translations
Priority one: what do the want, where are they from?
You'll be reporting to me, but you'll be working with him
when you're in the shell
That's what they're calling the UFO
Who's being carted off in the medevac?
Not everyone is wired for what you're about to do
So, what do they look like?
You'll see soon enough
Every 18 hours, a door opens up
That's where we go in
It's time
Yeah, that just happened
What happens now? - They arrive
They need to see me - Doctor Banks?
Are you insane?!
Now, that's a proper introduction
More objects have landed around the world
This is one of twelve
We never gonna be able to speak their words
You've got two days - Figure something out
I am human
It's their language!
We need to make sure that they understand
the difference between a weapon and a tool
language is messy and sometimes one can be both
Are you dreaming in their language?
Wake up, mommy
It's possible they're prodding us to fight among ourselves
This is just a way to force us to work together for once
It's more complicated than that
how is it more complicated
Russia just executed one of their own to keep their secret!
You got 21 hours before they start a global war
How do we clarify their intentions?
I go back in
Why does this feel worse?