Please don't make me go.
You can keep homeschooling me.
I taught you everything I know.
No more argument, okay? We
discussed this ad nauseam.
What's ad nauseam?
You don't know? Well, looks like someone needs school.
Good morning, Miss Stevenson.
Who can tell me what three plus three is?
Everyone knows it's six.
Mary, can you stand up, please?
Can you tell me what 57 multiplied by 135 is?
Okay. Who can-- - 7695.
The square root is 87.7 and change.
Now what does ad nauseam mean?
♫ I listen to the wind, to the wind of my soul
I think your niece may be gifted.
I am good friends with the headmaster of the Oaks Academy for Gifted Education.
No. I promised my sister...I'd give Mary a normal life.
I think she's gotta be here.
♫ I've sat upon the setting sun
Who's that lady in front of our door?
That would be your grandmother.
Holy sh...
It's a MacBook, darling.
What are you doing here?
You are denying the girl, her potential.
How many seven year olds are doing advanced calculus?
You forgot the negative sign on the exponent.
Mary, why didn't you say anything?
Frank says I'm not supposed to correct older people.
Nobody likes a smart-ass.
We petition the court to grant my client full custody of the child.
No!.. No!
You're gonna take that girl.
You're gonna loan her out to some think tank
Where she can talk nontrivial zeros with a bunch of old Russian guys for the rest of her life.
And you'd bury her under a rock.
Evelyn, stop!
I'm raising her how I believe Diane would have wanted.
♫ Do you need a reason ♫ We should commit treason
If anybody takes that baby away, I'll smother you in your sleep.
My sister wanted Mary to be a kid.
She wanted her to have friends and to be happy.
Tell us, do you have health insurance?
No.
Did you spend the night in jail? -- Objection!
What's your greatest fear?
That I'll ruin Mary's life.
Mary! -- Mary.
Mary! -- Uh-uh!
She's bossy.
I've heard that.
♫ Valleys of the young
He's a good person. He wanted me before I was smart.