We're the California Highway Patrol
This job is crucial
Without us out there...
... someone could get hurt!
The California Highway Patrol
think they have some crooked cops
They want you to go in the inside
Go into cover within the department, that's awesome!
We put you with a rookie name, Jon Baker
So who's my plan?
Francis, Llewelyn, Poncherello
Are the first two female names?
John, I like you,
you remind me of my husband
He's really...
handsome.
You've had 23 surgeries?
But you can ride a motorcycle, I'll give you that
Yes ma'am, like a mother
No
What's up, I'm Jon
Poncherello
Awesome man, we're partners
Let's kick this off with the real thing
you're homophobic or whatever, that's cool
No! You think I'm homophobic? Jon Baker, the baker?!
pretty badass
when you're all suited up for battle
well Looking like UPS drivers
Go brown, right?
This job is my one shot at saving my marriage
What are you wearing?
My uniform!
It's like you're 3 beers too intimate
I'm a tough motorcycle cop
I've got no emotion
What's your job?
Find the dirty cops
You're FBI?
Yup
Hey, we need to focus!
are you kidding me right now?
I'm just like kind of powerless when it comes to yoga pants
park and i ever visible erection
You think you can ride with that?
I don't know
We don't know who in this department is in on this
We're like Jay Z and Beyonce. We're ride or die!
I'm Jay Z
We're in pursuit!
What's your twenty?
I'm northbound
Ponch is southbound
Damn it!
You screw up this case
you're fired!
You've got a legitimate lead
oh We have a suspect's head, that's a victory
Nasty! Just damn nasty!
I need to get in some warm water
I'm not gonna care you, there!
I saved your life yesterday
Oh my God. I knew you were gonna bring it up!
Grab me and get it over with! Fine, fine
You face when my...
No, no, there is no contact
i could have sworn i felt either you know your nose or your lips
might been like a little bit of contact...