y'all want to see their robots
we're not supposed to be here
we're kids man we get away with anything
I was
just a normal kid
before my world fell apart
No! No! No!
look at me, wake up Canopy
Went to a normal school
lived a normal life
some kids just tease me
Wow.
Who is he?
As far as your concern my boyfriend.
How long has that been going on?
it's a...you run like a girl
we're family now
you're going to take care of you promise
just don't expect any bedtime stories
you throw like a girl
come on guys
you fight like a girl
Put him down!
You think I'm afraid of them?
You out of your mind?
You're not going anywhere with me
I want to stay, and I want to fight them
think you're badass huh
it is okay to be a kid little JLO
funny that you can do when all you have left depends on it
done
fight like a girl
yeah I felt like a girl
coming with me or what
don't you
we're going home missy
Turn around, what do you got in your mouth?
Drop the cruiser right now
come on man careful
you get back in your hole think about what you did