Come on, bud
There's a whole other world of dragons out there
Unbelievable
What do you say?
What should we name it?
Itchy armpit it is
I bet you think you know a lot about dragons
Should I know you? - No...
But a mother never forgets
Every dragon has its secrets
I'll show them all to you!
Did you know about this?
That's your mother?!
Now you know where I get my dramatic flair!
He likes you.
Something is coming. Something you've never faced before
What's down there?
I alone control the dragons!
Drago Bludvist is a madman
I'll bloody his fist with my face if he tries to take my dragon!
Dad, there's something you need to know
Oh, boy
I know what you're gonna say
You're as beautiful as the day I lost you
We're a team now
Now what do you want to do?
Drago's coming for our dragons
We have to stop him. Together
Don't worry, bud
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you
You have the heart of a chief...
That's my boy!
... and the soul of a dragon
You know that doesn't wash out
Cut them down!
Dragon riders coming through!
Heads up!
We can't fly these things!
They're babies!
They don't listen to anyone
Take 'em down, babe!
Come on, bud!
Hold on!
Distract the alpha!
Have a nice flight!
Yeah, baby!