I'm not gonna dress it up
Turkeys are dumb
Really dumb
You don't get it! They're fatting us up to eat us!
Hey! Corn!
See you later, Reggie
From the academy award winning producer of Shrek
We came to this farm for my favorite presidential tradition
Pardoning the Thanksgiving turkey
And the director of "Horton Hears A Who!"
Don't worry, you're safe
I'm tired now
This is your new home!
Pizza!
Does it get any better than this?
Hello, soldier
Whatever you do?
do not make a sound
You've been recruited for a top secret mission
What are you talking about?
We're going back in time to the first Thanksgiving
to get turkeys off the menu!
Who is talking to?
This guy, right here
He totally gets it
Look. See how he's nodding?
A map!
They aren't gonna just write "Time machine" on the...
Of course, they are
Control, we have a contaminant - Copy that. What type of agent?
Turkey, sir. How do we address it?
With cranberry sauce!
But seriously?
Let's go!
Wait, wait, wait!
Take us to the first Thanksgiving
Our mission is not to save ten turkeys...
Welcome to our home... but all of them
She wants you to throw up some worms into her mouth
What?
I will get those birds
Every last one of them!
Enemy approaching.
You must follow me blindly!
For the flock!
What's your plan for getting in?
I'll use my incredibly toned pecks and buttocks to throw you over the wall
Go!
Funny, right?
I'm sick of you throwing me around. You see this line?
Do not come into my personal space!
Did you not see the line? Cuz I was pretty clear....