I have been watching you
you have to remember.
I saw someone down there
it wasn't human.
He's a known terrorist
and he's killed again.
He didn't just kill them,
he hacked into their minds.
He is everywhere and nowhere.
will find him.
and I gonna kill him.
You never talk about your past.
I don't remember much,
just fragments.
There was an attack,
you were dying.
We saved you
and now you save others.
Everything they told you,
was a lie.
You had a family.
Remember that.
What are you?
What a beauty you are.
What do you want from me?
They did not save your life,
they stole it.
How many more there before me?
She was supposed to have a clean brain.
I ordered you to terminate.
They created me
but they cannot control me