Dad, this is my boyfriend, Martin
Pleasure to meet you Mr. Gallo
Nice to meet you, Martin
Martin is a musician.
The, uh, banjo
Like Kermit the Frog?
Mr. Gallo?
Is Jenny home?
We broke up
Any idea where I could find her?
I don't have an address
but I've been over there.
You want to get dressed and you can take me over there?
You know where we're going, You drive
Actually, I don't drive
We love Jenny
but some of us loved her a little too much
What?
A certain someone in this house
wanted to have sex with your daughter
OK, we should get going.
Hey, can I come?
You don't think she got kidnapped, do you?
So what is it that you do exactly?
We used to joke that you were an arms dealer
I'm in procurement
Look out!
So amazing when I was like
look out!
You're a real life saver
She'll turn up Mr. Gallo
You can call me Frank
I don't think I can do that.
This is a very bad idea
I need to see if my daughter is in trouble
Run
We've been searching for Jenny
all day and night
running from the police
I really don't need a recap, OK?
I was there
This happens every day
It's like that movie, John Wayne
This is not a movie, This is life
Nice work, guys
Would you mind just putting something out there
I already did it
You did what?
Tweeted it
"Baller old guy"
"Creepy young guy"
hashtag Random, hashtag Doable