Today's the day!
Our field trip
to the stingray migration
Stingray migration
Migration is about going home
Home!- Which is where you're from
How do the stingrays all know where to go?
Instinct. Something deep inside you that feels so familiar that you have to listen to it
My mom, my dad!
I have a family!
We will never forget you, Dory
What if I forget you?
I miss them
Do you know what that feels like?
Yes
Then we better get going!
Totally sick!
Isn't it great?
No, I'm gonna be totally sick!
Can you help me?
Sorry, not a great swimmer
I think you swim beautifully!
Thank you!
You're welcome!
Wait, Dory?- Yes
Dory?- Yes.
You and I were friends!- No!
It was so much fun: I'd tell you a story and you'd completely forget about it!
And then I'd get to tell it to over and over again!
I'm looking for my family
Are you crazy?
It's too dangerous!
Hands!- Hands?
Mommy?
Holy Neptune!
That is definitely not Mommy!
I'm sorry- I gotta blink
How do you hold your eyes open that long?
Hand, what's happening?
Hello?
Hey, you!
Hi, can you help me?
Not good