they're still on us
these guys are taking it personal
you were only supposed to create a diversion Roman
That was complete destruction!
what you want from me
I'm Roman Pearce, man! - It's what I do
phase two
phase two what's phase two?
bombs away
holy shh...
You know what i like about you Dom?
You're a genuine outlaw
But your family...
A hell of a job, brother!
We get back to the base, beer's on me!
...is about to go up against the only thing they can't handle.
You.
Did you ever think you'll even betray your family the way you did today?
Dominic Toretto
... just turned on us!
Well well well, would you look at that.
I don't know why he's doing this, but that wasn't Dom.
She's the very definition of "high-tech terrorism".
And now, she's working with your guy.
I think I found my team!
This should be interesting.
You wanna play like that?
Ouch
This is impossible..
Which is why, we're going to need a little help.
I will beat you like a Cherokee drum!
Well, took longer than I expected.
If you gotta catch Dom, you guys are gonna work together.
Surprise!
I just found love!
Hell, I've been waiting for this. We got a tank.
Let's roll.
Here they come.
I don't know if the old Dom is in there, but I don't give a damn. I am taking you down, Toretto.
Let's play.
Why are they shooting at me?
I don't know! Maybe cause you're in an Orange Lamborghini?
Shup up, Tej!
Oh shit!
We're gonna need a bigger truck!
Dom!
You're gonna turn your back on family?