How would you describe what The Circle is.. to.. say your grandmother?
It's the chaos of the web made...elegant
Speed Round Paul or John?
Early Paul, late John.
Mario or Sonic?
Early Sonic, late Mario.
Needs of the society, or needs of the individual?
Should be the same.
You're most scared of....?
Unfulfilled potential.
I am a believer in the perfectibility..of human beings.
When we are our best selves
The possibilities are endless.
At The Circle, there isn't a problem that we cannot solve
We can cure any disease and we can end hunger
Without secrets, without the hoarding of knowledge and information
We can finally realize our potential.
Circlers, do you like to share?
Sharing is Caring!
We...will see it all!
If it happens, we all know!
Imagine the human rights implications.
There needs to be accountability.
What is this?
The Circle has the power to change everything.
So many of our lies will get us in trouble.
Things we hide.
We care about everybody you care about.
Because knowing is good!
But knowing everything...
is better!