You all sacrificed so much to be here
and be a part of this thing we're doing
This crew is made up of couples
Its the first ever large scale colonization mission
everyone back on Earth is really grateful
for all your hard work
and your courage
We're making history here
It's sweet
What are the odds of finding human vegetation this far from Earth?
Who planted it?
You hear that?
What?
Nothing.
No birds...
no animals...
nothing.
What happened here?
Come in, do you read me?
What's happening?
I need you (gasp) right now
I need you...
...just calm down here, calm down.
Don't tell me to calm down!
You're breaking up
All of this
to start our new life
Where is it?
Let me out!
Hold on!
Holy...