come one step closer
and I'll illuminate you with a soft glow!
and I'll clean your clock!
ahhhhhhhhhh!!!!!
oh blimey!
herr hummm!
look you've all made a excellent decision to see this movie!
your clearly shrewd
so let me lay this out for you
on march 31st my movie DreamWorks The Boss Baby will be coming out!
we don't have any talking candle sticks, but if that's the deal breaker we'll cram one in there somewhere!
OH YEAH!
WHAT THE!!!
I think the kid might be onto me
hoh!
YESSSS!!!
YOU CAN TALK!!!
LET GO YOU LITTLE!!!!
Look the kids are finally getting along!
That's nice!
I'm on a mission
puppies are woman and babies are losing!
My job is to find out why!
Now I'll see if there's a place round here with decent sushi!
I'd kill for a spicy tuna roll right about now
I will help you just to get rid of you!
How do we get past the guard?
ARF!
huhhhh!!!
I DON'T WEAR Norco!
PUT THIS THING ON!!
What's all the racket?
isn't he adorable!
WHAT!
Bummer
I cant do this without you Tim!
we do make a pretty good team!
No literally I can't reach the doorknob
I can't reach the doorknob
I've never been so humiliated in all my lifffffe!
PUT THAT COOKIE DOWN
COOKIES ARE FOR CLOSURES!
DEAL!
I'VE GOT ONE FOR YOU TOO!