This is a message from the Collective
Are you overly tired or experiencing increased sensitivity?
Remember, physical contact
or displays of feeling are a danger to all of us
Let's do our part to help contain this disease
Did any body see that? - Anyone recognize her?
That's our first jumper in a while
I've been watching you, the way you look at the world
The way you experience things
it's has to stop
If it continues, I'll be forced to report you
I can't stay away from you. I can't not be around you
realize what would happen if anyone saw us
can't happen. You know that
Do not risk your job. Do not risk you life
I was told to keep an eye on you
Is there something you want to tell me?
He knows - What are we gonna do?
seriously considering this
If we stay here, we'll be found out
If you make this decision, there's no turning back
Just remember what this feels like