Never going to get it...
Look at him
Does anything about that look normal to you?
Let's rack him
Here, heavy
Well, there's no coming back from that
My man! - Yo, you better back up, man!
Calvin! It's me, Bob
Sorry, do I know you? - Robbie Weirdick from high school
God, man, look at you. You lost like 200 pounds!
What'd you do? - I just did one thing
I need to know
I worked out six hours a day, every day, for the last 20 years straight
You should know one thing about me...
I'm in the CIA - Are you joking with me right now?
Drop your weapon! Do it now! - I got a plan
It might get us both killed, but if it works it will be a totally boss story
Cool? - No. No, it's not cool
Cool - No, I said it's not cool
Three weeks ago an enemy of the state stole the encryption keys to the entire US spy satellite program
I need your super sweet accounting skills
to help me figure out the last piece of this puzzle
You're like a chocolate Google. Boop, boop, boop
Bob, don't do that. Stop it. Stop it
You were the coolest guy in school
You're my only friend, Calvin
You're the only one in this whole world that I trust
Now that you're in - I'm not in
I know. But they think you're in
But i'm not
Probably one of those perception versus reality things happening right now - No. I am out!
Which car are we taking?
Not that one - Oh my God
You chose to be an international CIA spy
Cuz I don't like bullies
You're like Jason Bourne in "jorts"
Did you see that pop?
I did the thing
I did the thing, Bob!
You remember those backflips you used to do?
Let's do the flip
That was so close