What the hell is your delay, Captain?
We're waiting, sir
Waiting for what?!
Private Doss
Who the hell is private Doss?!
I always dreamed about being a doctor, but...
Didn't get much school
I can't stay here while all of them go fight for me
Would you figured this war is just going to fit-in with your ideas?
While everybody else is taking life, I'm gonna be saving it
That's gonna be my way to serve
This is a personal gift from the United States government
designed to bring death to the enemy
Well, I'm sorry, Sergeant, I can't touch a gun
You don't kill? - No, sir
You know, quite a bit of killing does occur in war?
Private Doss does not believe in violence
Do not look to him to save you on the battlefield
I don't think this is a question of religion. I think this is cowardice
I fell in love with you because you weren't like anyone else
They're saying you could go to prison
But I don't know how I'm gonna live with myself if I don't stay true to what I believe
With the world so set on tearing itself apart
don't seem like such a bad thing to me to want to put a little bit of it back together
Private Doss, you are free to run into the hellfire of battle without a single weapon to protect yourself
I'm gonna get you home!
There's something you gotta see
Who did this?
"Doss, the coward."
We have to go back up tomorrow
The men aren't gonna go up there without you
Help me - You'll have to trust me
You better come home to me
Please, Lord
help me get one more
Help me get one more