I can't believe it's been twenty years
still gonna take your father to the anniversary
We wouldn't be here if it wasn't for him
On this day, in 1996
the world escaped the clutches of extinction
Your father was the bravest man I've ever seen
We all lost someone we love
But in their sacrifice we found the technology
to build a stronger and safer Earth
Because our survival
is only possible when we stand together
Oh, my God
A distress call
Why are they screaming? - They're not screaming
They're celebrating
They're coming back
It has its own gravity
What goes up, must come down
Shouldn't we be nervous?
Yeah!
Our whole lives built up to this moment
It's touched down over the Atlantic!
Which part? - All of it!
Make them pay
Not going up there to make friends
We've got to remind them Earth is not for the taking
I had years to get us ready
We're going down!
We never had a chance
We didn't last time either
We convinced an entire generation
that this is a battle that we could win
We sacrifice for each other, no matter what's the cost
And that's worth fighting for
It's the 4th of July
so let's show them some fireworks
Hold on!
They like to get the landmarks