So, you're just starting your day, or did you just get off?
They call, I go, you know?
So, what is it you do?
I'm a driver.
oh, Like a chauffeur
Anyone I'd know?
I hope not
What is your name?
Baby.
Your name's baby ?
B, A, B, Y, baby?
It's the one who listen to the music all the time
Is he mental?
Mental meaning slow, was he slow?
No.
He had an accident when he was a kid.
Still has a hum in the drum,
plays music to drown it out
and that's what makes him the best.
One more job and I'm done.
One more job and we're straight.
I don't think i need to give you the speech about what'll happen when you say no,
how I could break your legs and kill everyone you love,
because you're and know that. Don't you?
yeah
The moment you catch feelings
is the moment you catch a bullet
And your waitress girlfriend, she's cute.
Let's keep it that way.
I want us to head west and never stop.
You in?
I'm in, Baby.
These days, Baby,
you've got to get blood on your hands
Time to face the music.
Baby, we need to get out of here
I have to end this.
We're in bed together now.
Baby. Baby. Baby
Doc said Micheal Myers!
This is Mike Myers
It should be the Halloween mask!
This is a Halloween mask!
No, the killer dude from Halloween!
Oh, you mean Jason.
No!
Baby, you tell me who dies.
She a good girl. You love her?
Yes, I do
that's too bad.