Summer in the city of Arendelle
It couldn’t be warmer
it couldn’t be sunnier
But that’s about to change…
Forever
Arendelle! - It's completely frozen!
Cold, cold, cold...
A real howler in July, ja?
The land is covered in eternal snow
Really?
If we don't do something soon, we will all freeze to death
You want to talk about a problem? I sell ice for a living
That's a rough business to be in right now
I mean, that is really...
That's unfortunate
My lady?
This is awkward. Not that you're awkard. But just because we're, I'm awkard
You're gorgeous. Wait, what?
Hi everyone, I'm Olaf
Hi! - You're creepy
I don't want it. No!
We got off to a bad start
I know how to stop this winter
Hang on! - I like fast!
Wow, wow, wow, wow! Get you feet down
This is fresh lacquer. Seriously where you raised in a barn?
Let's go bring back summer!
Man, am I out of shape...
Wolves! - Duck!
Are you okay? - I've got a thick skull
I don't have a skull
Head rush!
It's so cute! - It's like being a baby unicorn
Now we just have to survive this blizzard!
That's no blizzard
That's my sister
That would have been nice to know
Heads up!
It is not
nice to throw snow people
Wow, wow, wow, feisty-pants, just let the snowman be!
'm calm. Great!
Oh, come on!
Olaf, you're melting!
Some people are worth melting for
Just maybe not right this second
Come on, buddy, faster! - No!
Olaf!
Hang in there guys!
I can't feel my legs! I can't feel my legs!
Those are my legs!
Hey, do me a favor. Grab my butt!
Oh, that feels better