Two options:
You either follow my rules or follow my rules, capiche?
- Thank you.
I could do it a different way.
That's fine. Thank you very much.
You're fired.
It's Christmas.
Yeah, I see the decorations
Good luck in the new year.
I just heard you play and I wanna ...
It's pretty strange that we keep running into each other.
Maybe it means something.
I doubt it
Yeah, I don't think so.
You could just write your own roles, you know...
Write something that's as interesting as you are.
What are you gonna do?
Have my own club.
Is that gonna happen every time?
I think so.
How are you gonna be a revolutionary
If you're such a traditionalist?
You're holding onto the past...
but jazz is about the future.
Maybe I'm not good enough.
Yes, you are!
Maybe I'm not.
It's like a pipe dream.
This is the dream!
It's conflict and it's compromise!
It's very, very exciting.
♫ Someone in the crowd could be the one you need to know
♫ Someone who can lift you off the ground
♫ Someone in the crowd could take you where you want to go
♫ Someone in the crowd could make you
♫ Someone in the crowd could take you
♫ Fly off of the ground
♫ You're the someone ready to be found